在新春佳节之际 少狼吧字幕组 祝大家 新春愉快 幸福美满~~
前情提要
Previously on Teen Wolf
那个本应该是锁着
That was supposed to be locked.
- 这是什么?        - 原子序数
- What are those? - Atomic numbers.
基拉
Kira.
我得拍张你的照片
I'm gonna take your picture.
证明我们曾呆在一起过
Proof of our time here together.
- 艾萨克 - 艾萨克 开门啊
- Isaac! - Isaac, open up!
哈哈
Yeah!
艾萨克?
Isaac?
艾萨克!
Isaac!
他冻着了 爸爸 现在他冻得跟块冰似的
He's freezing. Dad, he's like ice.
艾萨克 看着我 艾萨克
Isaac, look at me. Isaac.
他怎么了
What's happening to him?
加油啊 艾萨克
Isaac, come on.
艾萨克 听着 你得变身
Isaac, listen. You have to turn.
看着我
Look at me.
你得触发它 快 变身啊
You need to trigger it. Come on. Turn!
变身
Turn!
变啊
你看到他们了吗?
Did you see them?
谁?
Who?
有五个
They were five of them.
一身黑
They wore black.
我不能...
I couldn't...
我看不到他们的脸 被遮住了
I couldn't see their faces. They were covered.
什么意思?像面具一样吗?
What do you mean? Like masks?
其中一个...我能看见他的眼睛
One of them... I could see his eyes.
黄绿色的
They were greenish-yellow.
像是...
Like a...
像是萤火虫
Like a firefly.
防御系统没被触发
Security system wasn't triggered.
他们怎么进来的
Then how did they get in?
他们没进来
They didn't.
他们好像从阴影中走了出来
It was like they came out of the shadows.
你知道那代表着什么吗?
Do you know what that means?
爸爸?
Dad?
额... 我不太确定
Um... I'm not sure.
听着 你们两个...
Listen, the two of you...
我需要你们两个在这件事情上对外界保持沉默一会儿
I need you to keep this quiet for a few hours.
每个人吗?
From everyone?
一天就够了
Just 24 hours.
他们差点杀了他 爸爸
They could've killed him, Dad.
但他们没这样做
But they didn't.
我相信事出有因
And I think there's a reason why.
他们冲我来的
I think they might have been after me.
少狼吧字幕组
制作
翻译
南京 咖啡 XS zh
校对
小黑屋
压制
小龙
你什么时候到那儿的?
So when did you get there?
同时到的
At the same time.
跟谁同时?
At the same time as who?
跟我
At the same time as me.
巧合吗?
By coincidence?
巧合是什么意思?
What do you mean coincidence?
我在问你
That's what I'm asking you.
你们两个同时到达
The two of you arrived at the same time.
是巧合吗?
Was that coincidence?
在问我吗?
Are you asking me?
我觉得是在问我
I think he's asking me.
我想是在问你们两个
I think he's asking the both of you.
好吧 我来回答
Okay, let me answer the questions.
不对 我来问
Let me ask the questions.
刚才我总算弄清楚了
Just so I have this absolutely clear.
巴罗藏在学校的化学室里
Barrow was hiding in the chemistry closet at the school.
有人给他在黑板上留了信息
Someone left him a coded message on the blackboard
让他杀了基拉
telling him to kill Kira.
然后巴罗带着基拉去了变电站
Then Barrow took Kira to a power substation
把她绑起来企图电死她
and tied her up with the intent of electrocuting her,
并且导致全城停电
which blacked out the entire town.
听上去蛮对的
Sounds about right.
你怎么知道他会带她去变电站
How did you know he'd take her to a power station?
因为他是电力工程师
Well, 'cause he was an electrical engineer.
他还能带她去哪呢?
So where else would he take her?
只是个推论而已 斯泰尔斯
That's one hell of a deduction there, Stiles.
那我该说什么? 我学我爸
Yeah, what can I say? I take after my pops.
他恰恰在警局工作
He's in law enforcement.
斯泰尔斯 嗯 你 你只要回答他就好
Stiles, just, uh... Just answer the man.
我们猜的很准
We made a good guess.
你们两个在干嘛
What were the two of you doing?
- 吃比萨        - 吃寿司
- Eating pizza. - Eating sushi.
- 吃寿司        - 吃比萨
- Eating sushi. - Eating pizza.
吃了寿司跟比萨X2
Eating sushi and pizza.
你信么?
You believe this?
说实话 自从斯泰尔斯学会说话以来
To be honest, I haven't believed a word Stiles has said
他说的话我一句话我都没信过
since he learned how to speak.
不过我觉得这些孩子在正确的时间
But I think these kids found themselves
正确的地点实现的自己的价值
in the right place at the right time
坐在这的这个女孩真的是非常幸运
and that girl sitting there is very lucky for it.
基拉 你记得是这样子的吗?
Kira, is that how you remember it?
是的
Yes.
现在我能取回我的手机了么
Could I get my phone back now?
抱歉 不行
Sorry, but no.
基拉 等下副警带你回家
Kira, a deputy is going to take you home.
不过你先得完成这些文书工作
But we'll need you to fill out some paperwork first.
斯科特...
Scott...
我不知道你们为什么撒谎
I don't know why you guys are lying.
或者说为什么斯特林斯基愿意相信这些鬼话
Or why Stilinski is content to listen to this crap.
但是尽量记着
But try and remember something.
假若关于巴罗的这个故事有一半是真的
If half this story about Barrow is true,
那么不仅有人把他放了
then not only did someone help set him loose,
而且他只是这个盘游戏中的一个棋子
but he was a pawn in their little game.
一个杀人犯已经够糟了
A mass murderer is bad enough.
一个被人控制的杀人犯呢?
A mass murderer being controlled by someone?
更糟
Far worse.
好吧 我懂了
Yeah, I get it.
好了 回去吧 明天还要上课
All right, go home. It's a school night.
还有五分钟上课
Class starts in five minutes.
因为没电
Just because there's no power
别妄想学校停课
don't expect there to be no school.
三重否定 不错啊教练
That was a triple negative. Very impressive, Coach.
点赞
Copy that.
噢
Oops!
你好 你从哪儿来
Hello. Where did you come from?
不 不 停下 停下
No. No. Stop. Stop.
干嘛 我得和她谈谈
What? I need to talk to her.
不行 你得知道
No, you need to remember
有人留了信 让巴罗杀她
someone left a coded message telling Barrow to kill her.
所以我要和她谈谈
Which is why I need to talk to her.
斯科特 别介
Scott, no way.
在我们弄清楚她不是另一个
Until we figure out if she's just another psychotic monster
准备杀死所有人的疯魔之前
that's going to start murdering everybody,
我反对一切你跟她的交流
I vote against any and all interaction.
如果她喜欢我呢?
What if she's like me?
那个女孩承受住了12.1亿瓦特的电流
That girl walked through 1.21 gigawatts of electricity.
她跟你不一样
She's not like you.
就没有可移动发电机什么的吗?
Don't you have portable generators or something?
那不就是黑灯瞎火的聚会了吗 你又不需要这么多能源...
It's a black light party. It's not like you need a ton of power...
好 好 我知道了
Okay. Yeah, I get it.
黑光聚会?
Black light party?
不如说是被取消的聚会
More like canceled party.
我订的那个地方
The venue I booked
最少还要一天才有电
won't have power for at least another day.
你想帮忙找个新地方吗?
You want help finding a new place?
这重要吗?
What's the point?
这个城就不可能有电了
Nothing in town's going to have power.
不管怎么说 谢了
Thanks anyway.
你想开个万圣节趴么?
You want to throw a Halloween party?
然后呢?
What's next?
你准备加入到年鉴俱乐部?
You gonna join the Yearbook Club?
做点有意思的事吧
Just trying to do something nice.
干嘛? 谁会在意?
Why? Who cares?
他啊
He does.
你不懂 是吗?
You don't get it, do you?
斯科特根本不在意力量
Scott doesn't care about power.
他关心的是人
He cares about people.
你想加入到他的狼群吗?
You want to be a wolf in his pack?
努力做个高中生好吗
Try being a human in high school.
小甜心 看在这是我第一堂课
Sweetheart, since this is my first class
而且我五年没教书了
and I haven't taught in five years,
我只想提醒你一件事
I just want to remind you of one thing.
别让我难堪
Try not to embarrass me.
在说这些话之前你怎么不想想你今天穿的鞋子
You should've thought about that before wearing those shoes.
- 爱你      - 也爱你
- Love you. - Love you, too.
你妈干嘛教生物?
Why's your mom teaching biology?
因为哈里斯先生过去教生物
Because Mr. Harris used to teach biology.
直到他跳槽
Until his new occupation...
干人祭了
Human sacrifice.
啥? 我没杀他
What? I didn't kill him.
莉迪亚 怎么了?
Lydia, what?
那一夜
The other night,
我救了一些人
I helped save someone's life.
我觉得很棒
That felt really good.
但我看着你
And I look at you,
我只能想起你帮忙杀了博伊德
and all I can think is that you helped kill Boyd.
你不过是个坏小子 艾登
You're not just a bad boy, Aiden.
你是一个坏人
You're a bad guy.
我不想和坏人在一起
And I don't want to be with the bad guys.
我想我有个地方能让你办聚会
I think I know a place where you can have your party.
我现在不想谈
I don't want to talk about it.
好吧
Okay.
想谈谈周五的微积分考试吗?
Want to talk about the pre-cal test on Friday?
老师说题目都出自书上
The teacher takes all the equations right out of the book.
你有手机吗?
Do you have your phone?
我给你看个别人都没看过的东西
I'm going to show you something no one else has ever seen.
除了巴罗以外
No one except for Barrow.
给我拍张照 用上闪光灯
Take a picture of me. And use the flash.
哇
Whoa.
是
Yeah.
- 这是什么?    - 我不知道
- What is it? - I don't know.
几个月前就这样了
It started showing up a couple of months ago.
只有闪光灯开着才有
It only happens with the flash on.
我不知道为什么 但是巴罗知道这件事
And I don't know how, but Barrow knew about it.
他用我的手机给我拍了照
He used my own phone to take pictures of me.
这就是你想要回你手机的原因
That's why you asked for it back.
如果有人看到过这些照片
If someone sees those pictures...
我们得拿回你的手机
We need to get your phone back.
不给糖就捣蛋!
Trick or treat!
你说那个原来住在这儿的人去哪儿了?
Where did you say the guy was who lives here?
离开这儿了
He's out of town.
哦 赞
Oh, yeah.
这个能让你打开所有前门
Okay, this one will get you into all of the perimeter doors,
这个打开证物室
this one into the evidence room,
而这个打开我爸的办公室
and this one's for my father's office.
你不会是偷来的吧 是吗?
You didn't steal these, did you?
不是 我用充磁机复制的
No. I cloned them using the RFID emulator.
那不是比偷还要糟?
Is that worse than stealing?
更聪明好吗
It's smarter.
斯科特 我能问你些事吗?
Scott, can I ask you something?
好吧 我会乖乖...
Okay, I'll just...
你没跟他说吧
You didn't tell him anything, did you?
照片的事情
About the pictures?
没有 我只是告诉他你有些照片
Oh, no, I just said that you have some pictures of you on your phone
存在手机里 不想让别人看到
that you didn't want anyone to see.
什么类型
What kind of pictures?
裸照
Naked pictures.
真机智
Oh. Good idea.
行
Okay, cool.
好
Okay.
现在基本上大家都在为没有电而苦恼
Okay. So, now almost everybody's out dealing with the blackout.
不过前台还是有人的
But there's always somebody at the front desk.
值班室有一两个值夜班的
There's Dispatch and usually a night shifter or two.
你们俩得利用垃圾桶边上的服务窗口
You guys are gonna use the service door entrance by the dumpster.
懂吗 没人用那个
All right? Nobody uses it.
有任何人出现 我会给你发短信
Now, I'll text you if anyone comes out.
不过 斯科特 如果你被抓了 我无能为力
But, Scott, if you get caught, I can't help you.
我爸在接受被弹劾的调查
My dad's under investigation for an impeachment
就因为你爸 所以 发生什么事
because of your dad, so, if anything happens
我会跟你老死不相往来
I will run and leave you both for dead.
懂了 谢啦 真的 兄弟
Got it. Thanks. Seriously, dude.
我会问我爸 不过你懂的
I'd ask my dad, but you know...
嗯 我懂了
No, I know. I get it.
好啦 快去吧
All right, just, uh, hurry up.
基拉
Kira.
没电了
It's dead.
我们得带走
We have to take it.
不行 他们会知道手机不见的
No, they'll know it's gone.
那我们怎么给它充电?
How do we charge it if the power's out?
看看能不能找到充电线
See if you can find a charger cable.
太棒了
Awesome.
这是谁?
Who's that?
我
Me.
我和我爸
Me and my dad.
快点 快点
Come on, come on...
见鬼
Ah, hell.
快点 快点啊
Come on. Come on...
赶紧 斯科特
Come on, Scott.
好吧 我肯定会后悔的
Okay, I'm so going to regret this.
嘿 嘿 谢天谢地你在这里
Hey, hey. Wow!Thank God you are here.
天啊 感谢主
Oh, boy! Thank the lord.
你想干嘛 斯泰尔斯
What do you want, Stiles?
老天
Oh, jeez!
我就是 就是想了想案件
I was just... I was thinking on the case.
我想应该把我的想法告诉你
I was thinking I should clue you in on my thinking.
我是这样想的
Here's my thinking.
我想呢
I was thinking this...
我认为那个巴罗
I was thinking that Barrow, right...
我在想巴罗是在学校收到
I was thinking that Barrow received the information
要去杀谁的信息对吗
about who to kill at the school, right, you know that?
所以我在想也许是有人
So I was thinking maybe the person who
给了他信息
gave him that information,
注意这点
check this out,
也许实际上这个人
might actually be someone
就在学校
at the school.
这就是我的想法
And that's, uh, my thinking.
开机了
It's on.
你说的对
You're right.
-是吗  -是的
-I am? -Yep.
我们昨晚已经开始调查
We, uh...We started looking for links
巴罗与教职员和学生间的联系点了
between Barrow, faculty and students last night.
所以你已经 知道这情况了
So you already, then, know that stuff? Hmm.
你已经想到了
You already thought of that.
-你爸想到的 -哦
-Your dad did. -Oh.
他有用的建议之一
His one useful suggestion.
你知道吗 你对我爸的这种态度
You know, this attitude that you have toward my dad?
你可以装出一副
You can dress it up to all
看似很专业的样子
the professional disapproval that you want.
但我知道你讨厌他的真正原因
But I know the real reason why you don't like him.
就这吗?
Is that so?
是的 因为他知道了你不想让他知道的事
Yeah. Because he knows something
that you don't want him to know.
而且你猜怎么着
And guess what.
我也知道
I know it, too.
回家吧 斯泰尔斯
Go home, Stiles.
今晚有宵禁
There's a... There's a curfew.
我们做到了 所有照片都删掉了
We did it. All the pics deleted.
真是刺激死了
That was awesome!
我是说 有些怕怕 真的怕怕
I mean, terrifying. Completely terrifying...
但蛮刺激的
But kind of awesome.
我以前还从没有做过这样的事 你呢
I've never done anything
like that before. Have you?
做过 也就一两次吧
Yeah, once or twice.
我想我该送你回家了
So, I guess I should take you home.
嘿 你想不想去派对玩呢
Hey, you don't want to go to a party, would you?
德里克一定不能知道这事
Derek can never know about this.
你开心吗
You happy?
-非常 -很好
-Very. -Good.
现在该高兴高兴了
Now it's time to be happy.
这位需要涂一下
This one needs to get painted up.
脸还是身体呢
Face or body?
身体
Body.
我需要冰
I need ice!
我去拿
I got it.
好了
All done.
很棒
Nice.
早上它就出现在我的钥匙环上
It just showed up there on my key ring this morning.
我问过我爸是不是他放的
I asked my dad if he put it there
但他说他不清楚是哪的
but he said he didn't know anything about it.
-只是把钥匙对吧 -是的 但不是我的
- It's just a key, right?
- Yeah, but it's not mine.
而且我不知道哪来的是开哪的
And I don't know how it got there or what it's for.
你想我们离开这里出去想想吗
You want to leave so we can figure it out?
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween!
可以等等的
It can wait.
可以等一会儿
谢谢
Thanks.
-说什么 -谢谢
- What? - Thanks!
谢什么
For what?
所有这一切
For everything.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 我亲过你
Hey! I kissed you.
是的你亲过 你叫什么名字
Yeah, you kind of did.
What's your name?
我叫凯特琳
I'm Caitlin.
凯特琳
Caitlin...
我的天 你是凯特琳
Oh, my God. You're Caitlin.
我知道 我刚告诉你的
I know! I just told you that.
不是的 我知道 我是说知道
No, I know... I just...I mean, uh...
你和你的女友 她
You and your girlfriend. She's...
-她死了 -是的
- She died. - Yeah!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
-是的 我真的醉了 -好吧
- Yeah! I'm really drunk. - Okay.
你想跳舞吗
Do you want to dance?
当然
Yeah!
和真的不能比
Not as good as the real ones.
杀伤力也是
Or as lethal.
好的 当然 我活该
Okay, sure. I deserve that.
你怎么说都对
I deserve basically everything you say about me.
你要知道 是我把设备安装好的
But, you know, I was pretty instrumental setting this up.
全部这些吗?
All this?
如果我想去锐舞派对
If I wanted to go to a rave,
我会乘时光机回到九十年代
I'd get in a time machine and go back to the '90s.
你看见斯科特了吗
Did you see Scott?
是的
Yep.
你告诉他发生什么了吗
You tell him what happened?
没有 我们还有几个小时时间记得吗
No. We still have a couple hours, remember?
我们答应过我爸
We promised my dad.
你答应过你爸
You promised your dad.
我答应他是为了保护他
I promised him in order to protect him.
你答应的
You did.
我可没有
I didn't.
保护我爸是件坏事吗
Is protecting my father such a bad thing?
我不喜欢对斯科特有所隐瞒
I don't like keeping secrets from Scott.
不 你不会的
No, you don't,
你喜欢尴尬的站在这里
you just like to stand there awkwardly
等着有人注意到我们
waiting for someone to notice us...
无论我们是
Whatever we are...
然后你总是让事情
And then you like to make things
难以置信的不对劲起来
incredibly uncomfortable.
你什么意思
And what's that supposed to mean?
你觉得是什么意思
What do you think it means?
我想意味着你可能生气了
I think it means
you're probably mad.
-我没有生气 -没有吗
-I'm not mad. -No?
-没有 -好吧
-No. -Okay.
我很沮丧
I'm frustrated.
性事吗
Sexually?
不介意我用一下吧
Mind if I borrow this?
你是想继续聊斯科特
Do you want to talk about Scott
还是想在我的身体上作画
or do you want to paint my body?
我想涂你的身体
I want to paint your body.
哦 终于
Oh! Finally.
诡异
Awkwardly.
果然
Predictably.
斯科特
Scott...
Scott!
-是伊桑吗 -艾登
- Ethan? - Aiden.
伊桑去哪里了
Where's Ethan?
我也在找他
I'm looking for him too.
我都半个小时没见他了
I haven't seen him in like half an hour.
有什么不对吗
Is something wrong?
艾登
Aiden?
你有开瓶器吗
You have a bottle opener?
有
Yes.
你钥匙上有荧光粉
Your key has phosphors on it.
瞧
Look.
我以为你喜欢女的
Uh, I thought you liked girls.
我是喜欢女的 你呢
I do like girls. Do you?
-当然 -很好
- Absolutely. - Great.
-所以你也喜欢男的吗 -是的
- So you also like boys? - Absolutely.
你呢
Do you?
很抱歉 荧光粉是什么
I am sorry. What are phosphors?
哦 它们可以是任何发光的物质
Oh, they're any substance that luminesces.
在你的牙齿上和指甲里
It's in your teeth and your fingernails.
洗衣粉
Laundry detergent.
它也在这里
It's also in this.
在紫外线灯下它会反应所以会发亮
Reacts to the UV light, that's why it glows.
我是怎么把荧光粉弄到钥匙上的呢
How would I get phosphors on my key?
你有接触化学品吗
Have you been handling chemicals?
没有 我不认为我
No, I don't think I...
对不起 对不起 非常抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm really, totally sorry.
我刚想到些事 我必须走了
I just thought of something and I have to go.
真的 我想这样 我想留下
Really, I want it. I want to stay.
我本来整晚留下的 我发誓
I would just stay all night...I swear...
但我真的必须走 我无意冒犯你
But I really have to go and
I don't want to offend you.
-好的 -抱歉 我
- Okay. - Sorry. I just...
好吗 好的
Okay? Okay.
给你 你应该喝这个
Here. You could drink that.
全都喝掉 全部好吗
Drink that whole thing. Whole thing, okay?
不好意思 再见
Excuse me. Bye!
你沾了些涂料
You got some paint on you.
-还在那 -哦
- Still there. - Oh...
让我来吧
Ah, let me.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God!
我不敢相信你刚刚表现的和我妈一样
I can't believe you just mommed me.
我才没有
I did not mom you.
你绝对很像我妈
You totally mommed me.
好吧，可能有点像
Okay, I might have slightly mommed you.
你怎么能接受得了这些?
How are you so okay with all of this?
我给你看了那张照片
I showed you a picture
那会把其他人吓跑的
that would send anybody else running the other way.
对我而言看起来不坏
It didn't look that bad to me.
我看起来就像个恶魔
I look like a demon from hell.
我觉得我看到了其他的东西
I guess I saw something different.
你看到了什么
What did you see?
看起来 呃 有些东西保护着你
It kind of looks like it's, uh, protecting you.
就像盔甲一样
Kind of like armor.
而且对我而言也不像恶魔
And it doesn't look like a demon to me.
你觉得像什么
What do you think it looks like?
就像一只狐狸
It looks like a fox.
什么
What?
怎么了
What's wrong?
你头上有点东西
There's something on your head.
在你耳朵后面
Behind your ear.
转过来看镜子
Turn to the mirror.
看到没
You see that?
那是什么
What is that?
看起来像个数字五
Looks like a number five.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
艾登，过这来
Aiden, over here!
莉迪亚
Lydia?
莉迪亚 发生什么了
Lydia? What happened?
她怎么了
What happened to her?
我不知道，但他浑身发冷
I don't know, but she's freezing.
她体温过低了
She's practically hypothermic.
我们把她扶进去 帮我一把
We gotta get her inside. Help me.
去那边 那边有个暖风口
Over here. There's a heating vent.
我去找条毯子
I'll try to find a blanket.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
只有这样他才能自愈
It'll trigger the healing.
莉迪亚
Lydia?
他们衍生自黑暗
They came out of the dark.
看起来一样
It's the same.
一模一样
Exactly the same.
德里克?
Derek?
Bloody Beetroot是2006下半年成立的意大利电子和舞曲朋克的音乐形式
老兄 对不起Bloody Beetroot不接受要求
Bro, sorry, The Bloody Beetroot doesn't take requests.
老兄 说真的DJ不接受...
Bro, seriously. I said the DJ doesn't take...
他会听我的
He'll take mine.
滚出去!
Get out!
快滚远点
Get her out of here.
找到斯科特
Find Scott.
小伙伴们 他们都在看着我
Guys, they're all looking at me.
为什么他们都看我?
Why are they all looking at me?
伙伴们?
Guys?
你们做点什么啊
Somebody do something!
他们特么到底是什么东西
What the hell were those things?
你爸爸说的24小时到了
Your dad's 24 hours are up.
巴罗躲在学校的化学柜里面
Barrow was hiding in the chemistry closet at the school
有人在黑板上留下了加密信息
Someone left him a coded message on the blackboard
指使他杀掉基拉
telling him to kill Kira.